A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Graphic Services, Photographs, Special Events, Groups FA1155
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Graphic Services, Photographs, Special Events, Groups
1907-1973
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
FA1155
1.9 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Original order
Scope and Contents
Primarily contains 8x10 prints, with some 5x7 and 4x5 prints.
File Plan
Former Classification: I 526.1
Photographs
- Board of Scientific Directors, 1908; 1909; 1931; 1937; 1940; 1951 (Box 1)
- Hospital Nurses (Box 1)
- International Health Division (Box 1)
- Laboratories - Kenneth Goodner (Box 1)
- Laboratories - Fritz Lippman (Box 1)
- Laboratories - Duncan MacInnes (Box 1)
- Laboratories - Alfred E. Mirsky (Box 1)
- Princeton Staff (Box 1)
- Public Relations (Box 1)
- Services, Shops - Accounting Dept., 1967 (Box 1)
- Services, Shops - Electronic Shop, 1961 (Box 1)
- Services, Shops - Animal House, 1964 (Box 1)
- Services, Shops - Gardeners, 1961; 1963; 1964 (Box 1)
- Services, Shops - Glass Blowers, 1963; 1971 (Box 1)
- Services, Shops - Illustrations (Box 1)
- Services, Shops - Instrument Shop, 1961; 1964 (Box 1)
- Services, Shops - Media Service, 1961 (Box 1)
- Services, Shops - Power Hose (Box 1)
- Services, Shops - Laundry, 1965 (Box 1)
- Services, Shops - Purchasing, 1961 (Box 1)
- Services, Shops - Security, 1970 (Box 1)
- Staff - Non-Scientific (Box 1)
- Staff - Scientific (Box 1)
- Accidents, 1970 May 28 (Box 2)
- Adult Education Courses, 1965; 1970 (Box 2)
- Burning Nitrate Film, 1963 (Box 2)
- Christmas Lectures, 1959; 1960; 1964 (Box 2)
- Christmas Parties, 1963; 1965 (Box 2)
- Convocation, 1959-1962 (Box 2)
- Convocation, 1963-1965 (Box 3)
- Convocation, 1966-1970 (Box 4)
- Events - Dedication - Berlin Memorial Garden, 1964 (Box 5)
- Events - Dedication - Gasser Hall, 1925 (Box 5)
- Events - Demonstration on National Issues, 1970 May 11 (Box 5)
- Events - Dinner - Ettinger Award Dinner, 1963 May 29 (Box 5)
- Events - Dinner - Hotel Roosevelt, 1925 January 8 (Box 5)
- Unidentified Events, 1926 July (Box 5)
- Exhibit - Italian Exhibit (Box 5)
- Exhibit - RI Exhibit at Strasbourg, 1923 (Box 5)
- Installation of Dr. Seitz, 1968 October 8 (Box 5)
- Lecture: Gustave Stern Foundation Lecture, 1973 March (Box 5)
- Measuring Subway vibrations (Box 5)
- Meeting - Faraday Lectures at AAAS Symposium, 1967-1968 (Box 5)
- Meeting - Olfaction and Taste, 1968 (Box 5)
- Press Conferences - Honors - Paul Weiss, 1957 (Box 5)
- Press Conferences - Radio Pill Demonstration, 1957; 1958 (Box 5)
- Reception - New members of faculty and staff to meet trustees, 1964 (Box 5)
- Retirement Celebration, 1973 April 4 (Box 5)
- Retirement Celebration - Joe Tekverk, 1964 (Box 5)
- Retirement Celebration - Librarian - Judkins, Esther, 1964 December (Box 5)
- Retirement Celebration - Lupinek, B., 1961 (Box 5)
- Retirement Celebration - T. M. Rivers and Edric B. Smith, 1955 October (Box 5)
- Sigma Xi Group (Box 5)
- Summer Biology Program, 1960; 1961; 1965 (Box 5)
- Visitors to RIMR - Carrel and Visitors, 1913 (Box 5)
- Visitors to RIMR - Visiting French Ambassadors, 1918 May 13 (Box 5)
- Visitors to RU, 1964 August 3 (Box 5)